Guide to the Peter Megargee Brown Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Specific Legal Cases
  - Securities and Exchange Commission-In the Matter of The Boston Company Institutional Investors, Inc. et. al.-Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law of John W. Bristol & Co., Inc. and Objections to the Division's Proposed Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission-In the Matter of The Boston Company Institutional Investors, Inc. et. al.-Supplemental Memorandum of Respondent, Boston Company Institutional Investors, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission-In the Matter of The Boston Company Institutional Investors, Inc. et. al.-S.E.C.'s Initial Decision, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Briefs for Argument Before The Multidistrict Panel-Vols. I-II, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 1-2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Argument, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-The Boston Company, Inc.-Motion and Briefs, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-The Boston Company, Inc.-Pre-Trial Conference in Central District of California, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Second Argument Before Multidistrict Panel, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Litigation Index, Vol. I, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Briefs-Equity Funding Life Insurance Company, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Pretrial Conference No. 2, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Report of the Trustee, Robert M. Loeffler, 1974 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Cross Examination Notes for Raymond L. Dirks-December 1974-January 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Deposition of Raymond L. Dirks, Vols. II-III, 1974 (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Deposition of Raymond L. Dirks, Vols. IV-V, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Deposition of Raymond L. Dirks, Vols. VI-VII, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Deposition of Raymond L. Dirks, Vol. VIII, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-United States District Court for the Central Division of California-Hearing-Rule 12 Motions, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Rule 23 Motions-Oral Argument, 1975 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Digest of Deposition of John W. Bristol, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Memorandum of Contentions of Fact and Law of Lawton and Salomon, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Memorandum of Contentions of Fact and Law of Trading Defendants, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - In Re Equity Funding Corporation of America-Stipulation of Settlement and Final Judgement, 1977 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Application of John W. Bristol & Co. Inc. & III for Preliminary and Permanent Relief, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al., Vol. I, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Vols. II-III, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Vols. IV-V, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.- Vol. VI, 1978 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Vol. VII, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al. -Vol. VIII, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Vol. IX, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.- Vol. X, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al., Vols. XI-XII, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.- Vol. XIII, 1980 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Trial Briefs, Undated (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Coopers & Lybrand v. Walter Boschen, et. al.-Excerpts of Trial Testimony, 1979-1980 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Robert W. Preusch, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Robert W. Preusch, Richards, Ganly, Fries and Preusch, a partnership; Edward S. Fries; Walter E. Clough; Estate of Milton Ganly; "John Doe," and "Richard Roe,-Inquest Hearing, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Preusch, et. al.-Witness Sheet-Preusch, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Preusch, et. al.Trial Record-Vols. I-II, 1978 (Box 88, Folder 2-3)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Preusch, et. al.-Transcripts, Vols. I-III, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1-3)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Preusch, et. al.-Transcripts, Vols. IV-V, 1978 (Box 90, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Annual Conference of the United Methodist Church v. Preusch, et. al.-Transcripts, Vols.VI-VIII, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 1-3)
  - Jane De Roquancourt, Plaintiff v. Jacques De Roquancourt, Defendant-Action for Divorce-Vols. 1-II, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 1-2)
  - Aizer v. Pyne, Kendall & Hollister-Recission of Stock Purchases for Insanity-Arbitration, Vols. I-II, 1965-1966 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - In the Matter of Kreuger & Toll Company-Report by Guardian ad Litem, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - In the Matter of Kreuger & Toll Company-Peter M. Brown in his capacity as Guardian ad Litem-Cases, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Milton Liberman and Miroflector, Inc. v. Rubin Liberman-Arbitration-Close Corporation Dispute, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Teitler Milk Products Corp., v. East Smithfield Farms, Inc., 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Trial Memorandums-Teitler Milk Products, Gertrude Newcombe Steers, P. F. Collier, Inc., and Teitler Milk Products Corp., Undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Sara Blackburn, et. al.., v. Guy L. Goodwin and John J. Kearney; Lewis Cole v. Goodwin and Kearney et. al.-Briefs, Undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - SCC Investigation on Brooklyn Docks-Witness sheets [racketeering], Undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - SCC Interim Report [racketeering], 1952 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Brown and Seymour on the start of the new law firm, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- Church of the Heavenly Rest-The First Hundred Years, 1868-1968 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Church of the Heavenly Rest-Church Questionnaire of May 1972 (Box 96, Folder 4)
- The Order of Service for the Institution of Reverend C. Hugh Hildesley as Eighth Rector of the Church of the Heavenly Rest, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 5)
- Ordination of the Reverend Carol Linda Anderson--Saint James' Church--January 3, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 1)
- Eighty-Seventh Annual Dinner - The Church Club, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 2)
- 1976 Episcopal Church Convention-Minneapolis (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Installation of P.B. Edmund Browning, 1986 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Installation of P.B. Edmond Lee Browning, January 11, 1986 and Union Club Lunch E.C.F. (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Board of Regents Cathedral of St. John the Divine, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 6)
- Dinner In Honor of Dr. Henry A. Kissinger-December 6, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 1)
- The Saint Nicholas Society 152nd Annual Dinner-Dec. 5,1986 (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Abigail Adams Opera by Honorable Richard Owen, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Benchmark Award to Le Grand Vefour, March 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Information Submissions to Council for the Accreditation of Correspondence Colleges by British Institute of Engineering Technology and School of Careers, 1971 (Box 98, Folder 5)
- The Many Worlds of Sam Meek: A Legacy of Leadership, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Lawyers for Lindsay-Mayoralty Race 1965 (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Lawyers for Lindsay-1969 Election (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Report of the Commission on Alumni Affairs [Yale], 1970 (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Yale Class of 1944-Class Notes, 1969-1974 (Box 100, Folder 1)
- Writings of Others
  Speeches and writings of persons other than Peter Megargee Brown.
  - Citizens Jury for Better Judges by Whitney North Seymour, Jr., 1973 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - The Special Skills of Advocacy (John F. Sonnet Memorial Lecture-Fordham Law School), 1973 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Taking Better Depositions by E. David Robertson, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - United States v. Alger Hiss-Cross-Examination of Dr. Binger by Thomas F. Murphey, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - You, the Jury....In Re: Chappaquiddick by R. B. Cutler [Edward M. Kennedy and Mary Jo Kopechne 1969], 1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Practising Law Institute monographs relating to trial practice, 1961-1963 (Box 102, Folder 1)